{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "(Write) Define simple machine",
      "answers": [ "It is adevice", "make work simple and faster", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "(Write) four effects of force",
      "answers": [ "stop an object", "move an object", "can change shape", "can change direction", "all" ], "correct_answer": 5
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "(Write) What is gravatiational force",
      "answers": [ "Force by which earth pull an object", "Example, object fall down due to grav force", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "(Write) What is friction force",
      "answers": [ "Force that tries to stop a moving object", "Force by which earth pull an object", "both" ],
      "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "(Write) Wall is pushed it does not move. Work done?",
      "answers": [ "No work is done", "Work is done when object moves", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "(Write) What is solar energy",
      "answers": [ "Energy from sun is called solar energy", "Energy generated by flowing water",
                   "Energy generated by flowing air" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "(Write) What value mother show by using solar energy",
      "answers": [ "concern to conserve natural resources", "make best use of them", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "(Write) What is water energy",
      "answers": [ "Energy generated by flowing water is called hydro-energy",
                   "Electricity generated by flowing water is called hydro-electricity",
                   "When water falls on turbine it generate electricity", "all" ], "correct_answer": 4
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "(Write) Why is friction essential",
      "answers": [ "Friction helps us write on paper", "Friction helps us walk on road", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "(Write) Different types of simple machines",
      "answers": [ "Leaver, pulley", "Incline plane", "screw, wedge", "wheel and Axel", "all" ], "correct_answer": 5
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "(Write) What is lever",
      "answers": [ "rope over the wheel to pull object","Used to cut and lift",
                   "slope to push a load" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "(Write) What is Pulley",
      "answers": [ "rope over the wheel to pull object","Used to cut and lift",
                   "slope to push a load" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "(Write) What is incline plane",
      "answers": [ "rope over the wheel to pull object","Used to cut and lift",
                   "slope to push a load" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "(Write) What is Screw",
      "answers": [ "two planes joined to form sharpe edge. Knife, axe",
                   "Rod pass through center of wheel. Stee-ring of car", "Nail with a cut on it. Hold things" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "question": "(Write) What is Wedge",
      "answers": [ "two planes joined to form sharpe edge. Knife, axe",
                   "Rod pass through center of wheel. Stee-ring of car", "Nail with a cut on it. Hold things" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 16,
      "question": "(Write) What is Wheel and Axel",
      "answers": [ "two planes joined to form sharpe edge. Knife, axe",
                   "Rod pass through center of wheel. Stee-ring of car", "Nail with a cut on it. Hold things" ], "correct_answer": 2
    }
  ]
}

